

SANTIAGO ALZAMORA

WEB DEVELOPER FULLSTACK

ABOUT ME

I'm passionate about the world of programming. Through my experience, I've learned that teamwork is essential for achieving significant accomplishments and generating positive impacts. As a professional, I value effective collaboration and believe that working as a team is key to success in this field.

CONTACT

Adress: Mendoza, Argentina

Phone Number: 2615798364

Mail:

santiagoalzamora06@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/santiagoalzamora-12371520b/

GitHub:

https://github.com/SantiagoAlzamora

WORK HISTORY

Java Backend Developer

February 2023 - Actuality

Quinto Impacto SRL

Freelance Web Developer

November 2021 - Actuality

Programming Teacher

September 2021 - Actuality Egg Educacion SA

EDUCATION

JAVA Fullstack Web Developer

JAVA fullstack web programming course at Egg Education Institute (600 hs)

Advanced Programming Technicature (2 years)

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional Facultad Regional Mendoza (2021-2022)

Incomplete

Industrial Engineering(5 years)

Universidad Nacional de Cuyo (2018-2020)

Incomplete

LANGUAGES

-English: Advanced (B2)

-Spanish: Native

Skills

- Backend: Java (Spring Boot), NodeJS, socket(basic)
- Frontend: HTML, CSS (SCSS), Javascript, React
- Data base: MySQL, MongoDB (mongoose)
- Git, GitHub, Typescript